It was February 19th,
with Valentine's Day fever
still fresh in the air.
Soon, it'd be three months since I'd last
managed to get in touch with Mizuhara.
I thought I was good at going it alone
Would you prefer to go together?
Place
your finger here
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Heya! Some yoga pamphlet addressed to you got delivered
to me instead. Should I slip it through your mail slot?
Read
"Valentine's and Girlfriend"
She probably has me blocked.
I feel so stupid,
staring at this chat log forever!
Wait, I've heard that you can try gifting
stickers to see if you've been blocked.
You can't send this gift
blush
A hidden feature that will
only lead you to hell.
If you try to gift someone a
sticker set and it won't let you,
But it'd be best to not find
yourself in a situation where
you have to resort to this
Try this with a set you're
absolutely sure they wouldn't have ♥
that means they either have you
blocked or already own that set.
The original creator also tried this out,
and the app wouldn't let him.
Fiery Man Sticker Set
Pretty Please
But I'll never recover if it turns out
she does have me blocked.
I wanna know
That'd mean I'm just a guy she wants
to forget and move on from.
I don't wanna know
But I
wanna know
Maybe she's already with some other guy!
Are you texting any other guys?
I've got my hands full with you.
blood
Ugh! I opened Pandora's Box again!
Is my brain sentient?!
This is just self-harm!!
How many times must I hurt
myself before I'm satisfied?!
Ichinose Chizuru
Are you sure you want to gift this?
I did it
Phew. She hasn't blocked me.
I made it to the
confirm screen...
She is still ghosting me, though.
What am I even doing
How I'd love it if she said she was
digital detoxing for three months.
That doesn't explain her
pretending not to be home
You sent a gift.
Read
Hmm?
I gifted it!!
Come back!!
Come back
to me!!
Gah! I fat-fingered!
I'm some weirdo who gifts a sticker set
after being ghosted for three months!
Time to kill myself.
Yes?
Oh, it's just you. What's up?
snort
Raging bull...
What?
Ruka-chan?
That's what she told me.
She also said she feels bad
for doing this to you
Even though she pushed
you two to get together,
she was wishy-washy for so long,
but now she wants to make things right.
That's what Mizuhara was thinking?
So she doesn't hate me or anything!
But frankly, I didn't get
anything concrete from her.
If she knew how you felt,
she'd give you an answer of some sort.
That's what the Mizuhara-san
I know would've done.
She also said she doesn't know what
to call the feelings she has for you
that made her kiss you.
Yeah, she knew I was trying
to ask her out, too.
She did all that knowing how I felt!
I'm simple-minded, so I believe nobody
kisses someone they don't like.
Just personally speaking
But if she says she's not sure,
I can't really say anything to her.
I did what I could
Hmm? Master?
I'm so glad. So she doesn't hate me now.
Sheesh, this guy.
Thank you, Yaemori-san!
S-Sure!
I'll go talk to her!
All this time, I've thought
she rejected me.
I'm sorry.
I thought she thought I was a pain,
and the kiss meant nothing at all.
These past three months, I've been
telling myself she'd come to hate me.
But I was wrong.
Nothing could make me happier.
This was rock bottom.
Things can only go up from here.
If she knows how I feel,
then I'd like an answer from her.
I'll try to hear how Mizuhara
feels straight from her!
That's it! That's the spirit!
Yep!
You're looking like
a main character now
I'm cheering for you with all my heart!
Good luck with
your cosplays, too
Thanks!
Resolve and resignation are
two sides of the same coin,
but both always take lots of courage.
How do I get it
out of her?
Well, what now?
Should I text her an apology
for gifting her a weird sticker set?
Or should I go ring her doorbell again?
If I knock on her door and call out
to her, surely she can't still ignore me.
But the fact is, she ghosted me
because she felt bad for Ruka-chan.
Like our values
don't agree
or something
She might think I'm wrong for
trying to barge in on her after that.
Rental Girlfriend Agency
Kinoshita Kazuya-sama, your date
with Mizuhara Chizuru has
been confirmed!
Hey, I got it!
Mizuhara okayed a date with me!
We managed to confirm the schedule with the girlfriend you picked, so the date will proceed according to your booking.
What's going on? Is that confirmation
she doesn't hate me?
Did something change with Mizuhara?
But a rental date, huh? I guess
that'd make it easier for her, too.
I see. Makes sense.
Renting is how it all started,
so we go back to it.
Mizuhara...
Mizuhara!
March 1
Harajuku
Cleaned up
Gah, I can't! My head's about to
explode from all the nerves!
Here we have a virgin
holding his head
in Japan's trendiest town
I'm seeing Mizuhara for the
first time in three months!
Will I even be able to talk to her?
Uh, I'm sorry.
Nah, I'm sorry.
A date that's
not the least bit fun
No, I should be the one apologizing.
No, no, it should be me.
This is probably gonna be
awkward for her, too.
If I spoil the mood by asking
her why she ghosted me,
it's gonna suck for both of us.
Did she choose to go on a rental date
out of consideration for Ruka-chan again?
Over meeting outside work
That would add up with
what Yaemori-san said.
But that still means she's willing
to talk things out with me.
What will we even talk about?
About her pretending to be out?
About ignoring my messages?
Or maybe...
She doesn't know what to call...
It's all good! I made reservations!
I called ahead
to check
What's with that guy?
I even familiarized
myself with the area
Fresh off the boat?
And I checked out the route there!
There'll be plenty of time to chat!
But either way, we're about to
reach some kind of conclusion.
If she's not sure how she feels,
Just think about it
there's still a chance
she might reject me.
It's plenty likely that she'll just
decide she doesn't feel that way.
This is Mizuhara and
me we're talking about
But rejection doesn't scare me!
Not anymore!
Hey.
Sh-She's here!
It's Mizuhara
It's Mizuhara! Right on time!
She's right there,
for the first time in three months!
It's Mizuhara
She's so pretty
Wait, what do I lead with?
Hello? Long time no see?
Shall we head to the café?
Business as usual?!
What?!
So many people here.
That's Harajuku, I guess.
It amazes me every time
The new station building's so swanky.
What? Wait, what?
I liked the old one and its
retro vibe, but this is nice, too.
Huh? What?
She... She's acting totally normal!
Are you kidding me? How is that possible?
Sign of the times, I guess.
The world keeps changing.
blasé
unaffected
How can she meet me for the first time
in months and act like nothing happened?!
Whatever the reasoning
Wait, am I the problem?!
My brain's about to fry...
What? Aren't we going?
Oh, yeah, let's go.
I was spacing out
She doesn't know what to call...
Yaemori-san
said all that
No, that can't be!
But we're on a rental date right now.
Maybe she finds it awkward to bring
up personal stuff right now, too.
That makes sense
I'm glad it's nice and warm out.
I mean, yeah,
it's certainly not a fun topic.
I looked up the restaurant
because I was so excited.
As a pro, she might not want to do
it right away and spoil the mood.
Are we gonna talk
about it later, then?
But who knows when
we'll actually get to it?
She's gotta be looking for the right
time to broach the topic, too.
Today... It's gotta be today!
I'll get it out of her during this date!
I have to know how she feels!
I'll lead the way.
Follow me
Yeah?
What a pretty little café!
The perfect spot for afternoon tea!
D-Do you come here often?
For afternoon tea?
It's my first time here.
We should be able to have
a nice, long chat here.
We have an hour
and a half
This is your table.
What will you have for drinks?
I'll take Earl Grey.
C-Coffee for me, please.
She really is acting like
nothing happened, though.
I'm starting to think Yaemori-san
made all that up in her head.
But y'know, I'd expect a
"Sorry for ghosting you," at least.
But remember, we're on a rental date.
Can't bring up personal lives here.
Am I expecting too much?
2nd go-around
And damn, Mizuhara...
She's as pretty as ever today!
She has that versatile glow
that doesn't fade
Don't ask me why,
but that white sweater
goes hard!!
or stick out in a fancy place like this.
Ooh, sakura mont blanc and sakura monaka?
You can taste the spring coming!
If she steps out,
she's a classy girl who doesn't look
out of place in swanky Omotesando!
That white sweater plus coat is
max sweetness and femininity,
and she has the hots
to effortlessly pull it off.
That slightly short skirt
she only shows off indoors
is like a bonus track from the heavens!
This girl and I really did kiss, huh?
Here's today's special, the sakura
and strawberry afternoon tea set.
Wow, that looks amazing!
Whoa...
Don't be impressed!
I need to broach the topic quick!
We'll just
end up eating
A sip
Want some?
May I?
Not every day we have the chance.
Might as well taste everything.
Now we get a kiss of the indirect variety.
Maybe I'll
order it, too
Hey, this is great.
It's all-you-can-drink
Right?
No! Not like this!
Focus on the talk!
Mm, the quiche is so good!
The talk!
The crunch cake is out of this world, too.
I might actually really
like the sakura flavor.
I can't stop
thinking about
her lips!!
Heh... I went the whole hour
and a half without bringing it up.
Thanks for
the treat ♥
All I did
was enjoy this
classy moment in time
Today's Receipt:
Base Fee/hr 6,000 yen
Choice Fee (Regular) 5,000 yen
Traveling Costs 2,000 yen
Afternoon Tea 4,980 yen x 2 = 9,960 yen
Total: 28,960 yen
There's 30 minutes left on this date.
Can I really do this?
But if Yaemori-san's telling the truth,
that means Mizuhara's
trying to avoid the topic, right?
It's gotta be because she doesn't want to
bring personal matters into a rental date.
But if not now, then when?
If I let this slip, will I even get a
chance to talk it out with her again?
Yeah, I really can't let today end
without making things clear
one way or another!
I came here expecting the worst, anyway!
If we're gonna talk,
better sooner than later!
It's only a matter of time before
the fortress falls! No, it wants to fall!
I don't want to regret not saying
anything here for the rest of my life!
Go, me! Go for it!
Rent-a-Girlfriend
Where we split up
Is the station good?
That's the plan
Y-Yeah.
We have some time left.
Let's hang around here.
O-Okay.
The clock's ticking down!
I hate how pathetic I am!!
But it's too late to bring it up now!
Mizuhara was the same as usual
from start to end...
Just the usual,
super-pretty Mizuhara
Maybe she only okayed this date on a whim?
sparkle♥
Yaemori-san must've made up the part
about her knowing how I feel.
I believe
nothing
This is who I am.
This is who I'll always be.
Whenever I see Mizuhara, her beauty
overwhelms me and breaks my brain.
You're a really nice guy, huh?
I may say I'm not afraid of anything,
but when I see her smile, the idea
of her scorning me terrifies me
and leaves me forever unable to
take that step. Same old, same old.
I'm your typical "nice guy."
Nothing more than that.
Here.
Chocolate.
For you.
H-Hey, thanks.
Wait, what? Ch-Ch-Chocolate?
Valentine's was two weeks ago.
She's been wanting to give me this?
What does it mean?
If nothing else,
this is not a sign of hate.
I'm sorry for not replying to you
and avoiding you for so long.
I couldn't stop thinking about Ruka-chan.
And I felt bad for her, so I couldn't
bring myself to get in touch.
It's a little belated, but I figured
it was better than nothing.
Mizuhara... You really...
Yikes. I feel like I'm about
to cry for some reason.
So, uh... well, this is an apology?
All I'm doing lately is apologizing.
It's now! Now or never!
I... I heard from Yaemori-san that
you were doing it for Ruka-chan.
So I don't mind. Not at all.
Heck, I've caused you so much trouble,
I was worried you were
down in the dumps over it.
So I was kinda relieved when I heard.
I've been wanting to apologize
to you for everything
that happened on the trip, too.
I've been wanting to talk things out.
I get it.
I remember what happened in Izu, too,
and I know you only did it to save my ass.
It's not like that was
the first time, right?
I know I'm out of line saying this,
and that it's awkward for you to answer.
But I can't help but think that
that wasn't just you doing your job.
I want to ask you straight-up if
there was more to it than that.
Yaemori-san told me that you were
working through your feelings, too,
so I'm not saying I want
an answer right away.
But I meant every word
of what I said back then.
That's the Mizuhara Chizuru
I've come to love!
W-Well, see you.
Time's up, huh? Thanks for the date.
I'm excited to taste this chocolate.
I was really, really happy
to see you again.
Hold it in, dumbass!
What the hell? My body's giving up!
My hands are trembling.
My legs are quivering.
I'm finding it hard to stand.
Why am I this close to crying?
I don't have it in me to
hear Mizuhara's response!
I can barely hold it together!
I've had enough for today.
I said what I needed to say.
I told Mizuhara how I felt.
Wait!
Can I be honest?
Wait, what? Be honest, here and now?
She's gonna say yes or no—
if she likes me or not!
Frankly...
even I don't know what these feelings are.
"I don't know"?
Right, that's what Yaemori-san said.
She also said she doesn't know what
to call the feelings she has for you.
I do realize that it's weird.
I'm supposed to be doing my job here,
but I'm in so deep that I can't
talk my way out of it anymore.
And I don't know why I did what I did.
I'll have you know I spent these three
months trying to figure it out.
If any other clients found out,
it'd be a huge issue.
And mostly, the way things were
didn't feel right to me.
I even considered quitting
this rental girlfriend job.
Quit the rental girlfriend job?
Who, Mizuhara? Because of me?
B-But what about the money?
What about the bills?
That's why you're
doing this, right?
Honestly, it would hurt.
It does put food
on the table
This pays well and that helps,
and I only get a few acting gigs a month.
Plus, I like this job.
I could be a hostess or whatever,
but I know my way around this,
and letting it go would be a risk.
Y-You can't!
I brought all this on.
I couldn't take it if you fell
on your sword because of me.
I'll keep going, if you insist.
Cute!
But I'm not going to
sweep this under the rug.
I don't want to pretend any
part of my life didn't happen,
and I want to figure out my feelings
so I'll know how to in the future.
Mini-chan told me that
this is what a real bond is.
And it only leads to love,
as everyone else likes to call it.
Love? Then...
Then her answer is...
But think about it this way.
It's my job to be loved.
Huh?
You say you want me to play it natural,
but it's not like I'm showing
100% of my real self.
There are definitely parts I'm faking.
Telling me you love that version of me
just makes me go, "You're okay with that?"
Mizuhara...
I mean, you might just be in love
with "Mizuhara Chizuru," not me.
I don't think anyone's capable of
letting 100% of their true self show.
We're only human. There's always bound
to be some lies and fakery involved.
Yeah, maybe.
But I can't take that extra step when
I'm not sure about my own feelings,
and I want to pursue a relationship
like that only when I know I'm in love.
Yeah, she's out of my reach.
Ultimately, nothing has changed.
Even if I think we've gotten closer,
we're still rental girlfriend and client.
I can work up all the courage in the world,
and my feelings still won't get through to her.
It's not fair, Mizuhara.
Did we start off on the wrong foot?
If we'd met under normal circumstances,
would things have turned out differently?
But I can't go back and change that.
A kiss doesn't change anything.
Mizuhara will never be mine...
So, uh, I want you to give me
just a little more time.
Huh? Mizuhara, you mean...
I want to know, too.
I've never felt this before,
and I want to know what it is.
So, hey...
I'm going to look into it.
Anyway, I had fun today. Thank you.
Bye.
Today
Ichinose Chizuru
Thanks for telling me about the yoga pamphlet.
I'll go pick it up sometime soon, so hold on
to it for me?
"Thanks, bud!"
Read
Gotcha!
My memories are fuzzy
on what happened after that.
But I do remember that I actually walked
two and a half hours home from Harajuku.
The entire way back, I held myself
back from exploding with joy.
Whoa, that guy.
He's power walking.
And lastly...
Once I made it back to Nerima
and got away from the crowd,
I couldn't hold it in anymore.
Rawr! Mizuhara gave me chocolate!
Woohoo!
Hey! You're being too loud
over just some chocolate.
No, this is not just some chocolate.
It's chocolate that you gave me!
Okay, okay, settle down.
Now, next time on Rent-a-Girlfriend:
"Investigation and...
...Girlfriend."
I'm going out for another run! Grawr!
Hey! Wow, he actually went!
"Investigation and Girlfriend"
It made him that happy?